<resources>

    <string name="sensor_check_enabled_title">Riding smart check</string>
    <string name="sensor_check_enabled_summary_on">Application will use all possible sensors of the device to
        automatically guess if you are riding in moment of incoming SMS/call or not.
    </string>
    <string name="sensor_check_enabled_summary_off">Application will not try to detect if you are riding.</string>


    <string name="is_riding_assumed_title">I am riding now</string>
    <string name="is_riding_assumed_summary_on">Application will assume that you are riding now. If smart check is enabled, it will be not performed because it\'s reundant.</string>
    <string name="is_riding_assumed_summary_off">Application will assume that you are not riding. If smart check is enabled, it still can automatically detect when you are riding.</string>


    <string name="assume_screen_unlocked_as_not_riding_title">Lockscreen test</string>
    <string name="assume_screen_unlocked_as_not_riding_summary_on">
        If device has unlocked, screen, application will assume that you are not riding (because you are doing something
        on your device). If you will unlock screen during "Wait before response" delay, or sensor checks, application
        will stop checks, and assume that you are not riding also.
    </string>
    <string name="assume_screen_unlocked_as_not_riding_summary_off">Application will not care if device has unlocked
        screen or not.
    </string>

    <string name="wait_before_response_title">Wait before response</string>
    <string name="wait_before_response_summary">Application will wait with automatical response, giving you time to
        respond (or not) manually.
    </string>
    <string name="wait_before_response_dialog_title">Delay value...</string>


    <string name="include_proximity_check_title">Proximity sensor test</string>
    <string name="include_proximity_check_summary_on">
        If proximity sensor reports that device screen is not near something, application will assume that you
        are not riding (if you are riding, you should have phone in pocket - so device screen is near something).
    </string>
    <string name="include_proximity_check_summary_off">Application will not care about proximity sensor values.
    </string>

    <string name="wifi_check_enabled_title">WiFi test</string>
    <string name="wifi_check_enabled_summary_on">If your device is connected to WiFi network, application will
        assume that you are not riding (because being connected to WiFi means that you are in some building, so you are
        not riding now).
    </string>
    <string name="wifi_check_enabled_summary_off">Application will not care about WiFi connection status.</string>


    <string name="sure_riding_speed_title">Riding speed (km/h)</string>
    <string name="sure_riding_speed_summary">If GPS will report that you exceeded this speed, application will assume
        that you are riding on a motorcycle (For imperial units: 1 mile = approx 1,6km/h).
    </string>


    <string name="staying_still_speed_title">Staying still speed (km/h)</string>
    <string name="staying_still_speed_summary">
        Application will treat this speed and lower speeds as staying still. Best if it is like 3km/h, because sometimes
        GPS report speed up to 3km/h when you are staying still in reality (For imperial units: 1 mile = approx
        1,6km/h).
    </string>


    <string name="quick_speed_check_duration_title">Short GPS check duration (s)</string>
    <string name="quick_speed_check_duration_summary">
        Application will try to measure your speed by GPS for this amount of seconds.
        If it will fail (timeout), application will assume that you are inside building, without GPS signal.
        This value should be adjusted, to make GPS always fail inside building, and always succeed outside building.
    </string>


    <string name="long_speed_check_duration_title">Long GPS check duration (s)</string>
    <string name="long_speed_check_duration_summary">
        If first test will succeed to measure your speed, but it will be slower than "Riding speed", application will
        perform longer GPS test, to see if you are not staying in front of the traffic lights.
        This value should be adjusted, to let you enough time to have green light and start riding, before long GPS
        check
        will be timeouted.
    </string>


    <string name="required_accuracy_title">GPS accuracy (meters)</string>
    <string name="required_accuracy_summary">
        GPS result must be equally or more accurate than this value, to finish short and long GPS check.
        Smaller value is more accurate. Depending on GPS sensor on your device, very high accuracies can be impossible
        to achieve and cause timeouts everytime, even when you are really riding.
    </string>

    <string name="include_accelerometer_check_title">Accelerometer test</string>
    <string name="include_accelerometer_check_summary_on">Application will not respond automatically, if accelerometer
        will not detect shakes (device laying still suggest that you are not riding, usually during ride there are some
        shakes).
    </string>
    <string name="include_accelerometer_check_summary_off">Application will not care about values from accelerometer.
    </string>


    <string name="acceleration_required_for_motion_title">Shakes acceleration (m/s)</string>
    <string name="acceleration_required_for_motion_summary">Accelerometer must report higher acceleration than this value,
        to assume that device is not laying still and you are possibly riding.
    </string>

</resources>
