<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Motoresponder</string>

    <!-- widget -->
    <string name="widget_on_off_label">Motoresponder\'s assume riding setting</string>

    <!-- notifications -->
    <string name="debug_notification_title_text">Motoresponder debug</string>
    <string name="debug_notification_short_text">Close other notifications to see details.</string>

    <string name="summary_notification_title_text">Motoresponder</string>
    <string name="summary_notification_short_text" formatted="false">Auto response sent to %recipient%.</string>
    <string name="summary_notification_big_text" formatted="false">Auto response sent to %recipient% because you was
        riding when you got a SMS/call.
    </string>
    
      <string name="power_save_notification_title_text">Motoresponder</string>
    <string name="power_save_notification_short_text" formatted="false">Power save mode - app is off.</string>
    <string name="power_save_notification_big_text" formatted="false">You got some message/call but phone is in power save mode, so Motoresponder is turned off to save your battery.
    </string>

    <string name="ongoing_notification_title_text">Motoresponder</string>
    <string name="ongoing_notification_big_text">Motoresponder is trying to determine if you are riding now or not.
    </string>

    <string name="ongoing_notification_is_riding_assumed_title_text">Riding mode </string>
    <string name="ongoing_notification_is_riding_assumed_big_text">You set that you are riding now. Application will respond to every unanswered call and SMS. Tap this to turn off this mode.</string>

    <string name="settings_activity_label">Motoresponder settings</string>

    <string name="main_preferences_title">Basic settings</string>
    <string name="main_preferences_summary">Basic settings of application.</string>

    <string name="riding_preferences_title">Riding detection settings</string>
    <string name="riding_preferences_summary">Here you can configure parameters of riding detection, according to your
        needs.
    </string>

    <string name="number_rules_preferences_title">Contacts filtering settings</string>
    <string name="number_rules_preferences_summary">Here you can configure to which contacts or groups application
        can automatically respond.
    </string>

    <string name="how_it_works_preferences_title">How it works?</string>
    <string name="how_it_works_preferences_summary">Here you can see how application works, or view log, or read
        information about author.
    </string>


    <string name="disclaimer_title">Accept Motoresponder disclaimer</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_message">
        Authors of Motoresponder made all efforts to make it working as best as it can (we are using it on daily
        basis).\n\n

        But it is possible that application has some bugs inside. \n\n

        Because application operate on a little bit risky field, which is automatic responding for incoming SMS and
        calls, we advice caution with using it in case of very expensive phone subscription. \n\n

        Application has functionality of sharing your location with choosen group of people (when you are riding, and
        they are asking for it). It is disabled by default. Please take care during configuring it, because otherwise
        people who shouldn\'t know your location, will be able to get it. \n\n

        We give to you application for free, \"as it is\" and even if we make all efforts to make it perfect, your are
        using it on your own risk. \n\n

        So, authors can\'t be responsible to any damages made by application.\n\n
        If you don\'t accept this, please don\'t use application, and uninstall it. \n\n

        Authors of Motoresponder deeply believe that nobody should disturb you, when you enjoy riding on your bike.
        But some sort of people who never ride a motorcycle, never understand simple fact that (unless you have
        headset/intercom) you can\'t answer them when you are riding, and if we are not answering, it means that we
        are riding. They will call us fifteen times, until you will stop a motorcycle, and answer them.
        This application is solving this problem. Enjoy your ride! \n\n

        Credits: Orzech &amp; Medziku
    </string>
    <string name="disclaimer_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_reject">Reject</string>


</resources>
