<resources>
    <string name="settings_wizard_label">Motoresponder quick setup</string>

    <string name="wizard_sensor_check_title">Intelligent detection of motorcycle ride</string>
    <string name="wizard_sensor_check_description">If you want, application can detect when you are riding on a
        motorcycle
        automatically. Don\'t worry, it doesn\'t consume a lot of battery. You can just turn it on, and forget about it,
        it will magically detect when you are riding, and then application will automatically respond to SMSes and
        calls. \n\nIf you don\'t want, you can manually turn application to a riding mode (then it will answer) with a
        nice widget (you need to add it by yourself).
    </string>
    <string name="wizard_sensor_check_yes_label">Yes, use intelligent detection</string>
    <string name="wizard_sensor_check_no_label">No, I will set this manually</string>
    
    
    
    <string name="wizard_hold_phone_in_pocket_title">Where you put phone during ride?</string>
    <string name="wizard_hold_phone_in_pocket_description">If you put phone in tight pocket, please choose "pocket" option.
    Example of such pocket is jacket's pocket, or pants' pocket. \n\n
    If you put phone into backpack, bag, or you have phone mount for motorcycle, please choose "somewhere else" option.\n\n
    (Purpose of this: If you put phone in pocket when you are riding, application can assume that you are not riding everytime
    when proximity sensor reports that there is nothing touching the screen)
    </string>
    <string name="wizard_hold_phone_in_pocket_yes_label">In pocket</string>
    <string name="wizard_hold_phone_in_pocket_no_label">Somewhere else</string>


    <string name="wizard_custom_dialer_messenger_title">Limiting responses</string>
    <string name="wizard_custom_dialer_messenger_description">Application limit autoresponses, to prevent too much
        charge of your mobile account. There is two methods of doing this:\n\n
        Response based - after sending autoresponse, application will not respond given number until you will contact
        this number manually by sending SMS or calling (Caution: not working if you have custom dialer application or
        custom SMS application)\n\n
        Time based - application will allow to send only one response to given number in given time. For example max.
        one answer per 30 minutes.
    </string>
    <string name="wizard_custom_dialer_messenger_yes_label">Use response based limit</string>
    <string name="wizard_custom_dialer_messenger_no_label">Use time based limit</string>


    <string name="wizard_geolocation_title">Allow other people to ask for your location?</string>
    <string name="wizard_geolocation_description">This function allow to respond people who are asking you by SMS
        questions
        like \"Hey? Where are you?\" with your current position on Google map. Of course it works only when you are
        riding.\n\n

        You can configure group of people which are allowed to get such information in settings, probably it shouldn\'t
        share your location with everyone. You can also edit patterns which will be interpreted as question about
        your position.\n\n


    </string>
    <string name="wizard_geolocation_yes_label">Yes, sure</string>
    <string name="wizard_geolocation_no_label">No, thanks</string>


    <string name="wizard_when_app_not_work_title">That\'s all</string>
    <string name="wizard_when_app_not_work_description">Aplication is configured now. If you need to adjust it more,
        there is plenty of settings available for customization.\n
        If you choose manual mode, remember to set application into riding mode before ride.\n
        If you use intelligent detection, just leave GPS on in device\'s settings.\n

        Some of those cases can be resolved with proper menu setting. If you need advice, or you are interested about
        how application works, you can read more in settings menu.\n\n
        If you like application, it will be very nice, if you will rate application on Google Play :-)\n\n
        Enjoy riding :-)
    </string>
    <string name="wizard_when_app_not_work_yes_label">Okay</string>
    
</resources>
